Richard Rodgers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-18, Box 22-45)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-18)
    - No Strings (1962) lyrics by Richard Rodgers
      - Intro. to scene change, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p.; Note: some orchestration indicated (Box-folder 11/8)
      - La-la-la, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Loads of love, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Loads of love, Holograph sketch in pencil, including crossed out material titled "Lovely love"; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Look no further, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Look no further, Holograph sketches in pencil; [1] p.; Note: unidentified holograph sketch material at top (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Look no further, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Love makes the world [go], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; On cover page: crossed out unidentified holograph sketch material with lyric (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Love makes the world [go], Holograph lead sheets (2) in pencil; [1] p. each; On t.p.: "1961 No Strings" (Box-folder 11/12)
      - I do like Maine, Holograph in pencil; [3] p.; Uniform title: Maine (Box-folder 11/13)
      - The man who has everything, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Man who has everything, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/4)
      - No strings, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 11/15)
      - No strings, Holograph lead sheet (no lyric) and sketches (some lyrics) in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, 1 line crossed out; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/15)
      - Nobody told me, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 11/16)
      - Nobody told me, Holograph lead sheet (no lyric) and sketch in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/16)
      - [An] orthodox fool, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 11/17)
      - [An] orthodox fool, Holograph sketch in ink & pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 11/17)
      - The sweetest sounds, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 11/18)
      - The sweetest sounds, Holograph sketch in pencil, some lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/18)
      - Yankee, go home!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Note: not used in the show; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p.; Laid in: holograph sketch in pencil titled "Yankee" and unidentified crossed out material (Box-folder 11/19)
      - You don't tell me, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 11/20)
      - [You don't tell me], Holograph sketch in pencil, some lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 11/20)
      - [Sketches for No Strings], Holograph sketches in pencil, some lyric; [1] p.; Includes: "How sad" and unidentified (Box-folder 11/21)
      - [Lyric sketches], Holograph lyric sketches in pencil and typed; [47] p. total; Includes: Be my host [Eager beaver] How sad [La-la-la] Loads of love [Look no further] [Love makes the world go] [The man who has everything] Money makes the world go [No strings] Nobody told me [An orthodox fool] The sweetest sounds [Yankee, go home] You don't tell me (Box-folder 11/22)
      - [Lyrics], Red binder containing typed lyric sheets; [17] p.; Includes: Be my host Eager beaver How sad La-la-la (french and english lyrics) Loads of love Look no further Love makes the world go Maine The man who has everything No strings Nobody told me An orthodox fool The sweetest sounds You don't tell me (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Oklahoma! (1943; film 1955) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - All er nothin!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet for "All er nuthin"; [3] p. (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Boys and girls [like you and me], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Note: melodic sketch fragment at end; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/2)
      - The farmer and the cowman, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/3)
      - I cain't say no, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/4)
      - I cain't say no, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/4)
      - A scandal for the jaybirds, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in pencil; 3 p.; Uniform title: It's a scandal! It's a outrage! (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Kansas City, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Lonely little room, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Lonely room (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Many a new day, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet with verse typed on; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Oh, what a beautiful mornin', Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Oklahoma, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [5] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Out of my dreams, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/11)
      - [Out of my dreams], Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/11)
      - People will say we're in love, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Verse People will say, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Pore Jud is daid, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Poor Jud, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/13)
      - The surrey with the fringe on top, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/14)
      - When I go out walkin' with my baby, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/15)
      - [Sketches for Oklahoma!], Holograph sketches in pencil; [6] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[Oh, what a] beautiful morning" p. [3]: "[The surrey with the fringe on top]: Surrey middle" p. [4]: "[The surrey with the fringe on top]: Verse Surrey" p. [5]: "[Wait till you see her]" (from By Jupiter), "[I cain't say no]," "[The] surrey [with the fringe on top]" p. [6]: "[Oh, what a beautiful morning]: Verse Beautiful morning," "[Many a new day]" (Box-folder 12/16)
    - On Your Toes (1936; film 1939) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Glad to be unhappy see: [Sketches for Jumbo] see: [M.S. 10] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - The heart is quicker than the eye see: [Sketches for On Your Toes]
      - It's got to be love see: [Sketches for Jumbo]
      - On your toes see: [Sketches for On Your Toes]
      - Our private olympic games, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Note: previously unknown song, probably unused (Box-folder 12/17)
      - [La Princesse Zenobia ballet], Holograph sketches in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/18)
      - 10th avenue lead See also: [M.S. 9] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph sketch in pencil; [6] p.; Uniform title: Slaughter on Tenth Avenue (Box-folder 12/19)
      - There's a small hotel see: [Sketches for Jumbo]
      - Questions and answers, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p.; Uniform title: The three B's (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Too good for the average man see: [M.S. 10] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Two-a-day for Keith, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/21)
      - [Sketches for On Your Toes], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[The heart is] quicker than the eye" p. [2]: "[On your toes]," "[Chopsticks]" (Box-folder 12/22)
    - One Dam Thing After Another (1927) musical revue, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Dance negre, Holograph piano score in pencil; 5 p.; Note: cut before opening of the show; Uniform title: Danse grotesque à la nègre (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Opening act I: sandwich girls, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; Uniform title: The election (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Make hey! Make hey! see: [Sketches for One Dam Thing After Another]
      - My heart stood still see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Progress, Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p.; Note: probably minuet variation on "Make hey! Make hey!" (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Shakespeare, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; Note: probably variation on "Make hey! Make hey!" (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Shakespeare Dance, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p.; Note: probably variation on "Make hey! Make hey!" (Box-folder 12/26)
      - [Sketches for One Dam Thing After Another], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[Make] hey! [Make] hey!," "[The election]: Opening" p. [2] (upside down): "[My heart stood still]," "[When I go on the stage]" (from She's My Baby) p. [4]: "[Someone should tell them]" (cut from A Connecticut Yankee, the music later appeared in America's Sweetheart as "There's so much more") (Box-folder 12/27)
    - Pal Joey (1940; film 1957) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Bewitched, [bothered and bewildered] See also: [M.S. 12] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/28)
      - Chicago see: A great big town
      - Den of iniquity, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/29)
      - Do it the hard way, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/30)
      - The flower garden of my heart, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/31)
      - A great big town, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Happy hunting horn see: [Sketches for Pal Joey]
      - I could write a book, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/33)
      - I'm talking to my pal, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/34)
      - Plant you now, dig you later See also: [M.S. 12] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Take him See also: [M.S. 12] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/36)
      - That terrific rainbow, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/37)
      - You mustn't kick it around, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 12/38)
      - Zip!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/39)
      - [Sketches for Pal Joey], Holograph sketches in pencil; [9] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[Do it the] hard way" p. [3]: "Lolita" (from They Met In Argentina?), "I could write a book," "You mustn't kick it around" p. [4]: "[That terrific rainbow]: Color me," "Zip" p. [5]: "[That terrific rainbow]: Red hot" p. [6]: "Fisher" p. [8]: "[If] the twig's bent" p. [9]: "[Happy hunting horn]: Verse Hunting horn" (Box-folder 12/40)
    - Peg o' My Heart (1933) film
      - When you're falling in love with the Irish see: [Sketches for I Married an Angel]
    - Peggy-Ann (1926) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Act I finale, Holograph piano score/sketch in pencil; [3] p.; Note: includes or mentions "Where's that rainbow?," "[A little birdie told me so]: Birdie song," "Wedding march," "[A] tree in the park"; On back: 2 measure sketch in pencil (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Store opening, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Uniform title: Charming, charming (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Chuck it! See also: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 7 p.; Note: cut from Lido Lady and used here (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Dummy march see: [Sketches for Betsy]
      - Give this little girl a hand see: [Sketches for Peggy-Ann]
      - Hello see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Howdy to Broadway, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, partial lyric; 2 p. (incomplete); Uniform title: Howdy Broadway (Box-folder 13/4)
      - A little birdie told me so see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Paris is really divine, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Peggy! Peggy!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Tramping along see: [Sketches for Betsy]
      - A tree in the park see: [Sketches for Peggy-Ann]
      - [Sketches for Peggy-Ann], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "[A] tree in [the] park" p. [2]: "Give [this] little girl a hand," "[A] little birdie told me so" (Box-folder 13/7)
      - [Sketches for Peggy-Ann] See also: "My Clementine" in NON-SHOW MUSIC, Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: sketch #1: Howdy, Broadway sketch #4: Clementine (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Pipe Dream (1955) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - All at once: verse, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: All at once you love her (Box-folder 13/8)
      - All at once, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Uniform title: All at once you love her (Box-folder 13/8)
      - All kinds of people, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Bum's opera, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Bum's opera See also: "Tide pool", Holograph sketch in pencil, some lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Everybody's got a home [but me], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [5] p. (Box-folder 13/11)
      - The happiest house on the block, Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/12)
      - How long? see: [Sketches for Pipe Dream]
      - I am a witch, Holograph piano-vocal sketch in pencil, with lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/13)
      - On a lopsided bus, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 8 p.; Uniform title: A lopsided bus (Box-folder 13/14)
      - [The] man I used to be: verse, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 13/15)
      - The man I used to be, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/15)
      - The next time it happens, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 13/16)
      - [The next time it happens], Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 13/16)
      - The party that we're going to have tomorrow night, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Suzy development: 1 and 2, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [5] p. (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Suzy development, Holograph sketch in pencil, some lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Suzy is a good thing: verse, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Suzy is a good thing, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Sweet Thursday, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p. (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Thinkin', Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 13/21)
      - The tide pool, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [5] p. (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Tide pool, Holograph sketch in pencil, with lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/22)
      - [Tide pool], Holograph sketch in pencil; 4 p.; Note: different version than above, but some lyric is the same; On front: holograph sketch in pencil (crossed out) for "Bums opera" (Box-folder 13/22)
      - [Sketches for Pipe Dream], Holograph sketches in pencil; [15] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "All kinds of people" p. [2]: "[A lopsided] bus" (2 measures), "[Sweet Thursday]: Sweet Thursday interlude" p. [3]: "All kinds of people" p. [4]: "The man I used to be," "Su[zy] is a good thing" p. [5]: "[The] party [that we're gonna have] tomorrow night" p. [6]: "Sweet Thursday: ch[orus]" p. [7]: "[All at once you love her]: Guitar song?," "[A lopsided bus]: Bus?" p. [8]: "[A lopsided] bus: verse" p. [9]: "[The] man I used to be" p. [10]: "How long" p. [11]: "[The man I used to be]" p. [12]: "[Ev'rybody's got a home but me]: Everybodys got a house" p. [13-14]: "[A lopsided bus]: Remarkable bus" p. [15]: "[Untitled]" (written for, but not used in Pipe Dream) (Box-folder 13/23)
    - The Play's the Thing (n.d)
      - Music & the emotions, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Music & the emotions, Holograph (Lorenz Hart) lyric sheet in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Ope[ning] act I, Holograph sketch in pencil; [4] p.; Typed lyric sheet for "Opening of act I," annotation in pencil; 2 p.; Ms. lyric sheet [Lorenz Hart's?] in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 13/25)
      - [Lyrics for The Play's the Thing], Holograph (Lorenz Hart) lyric sheets/script in pencil; [16] p. total (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Please! (1933) revue
      - Rhythm see: [Sketches for Babes in Arms] see: Rhythm! in The Show Is On
    - Present Arms (1928) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - [Various titles] see: [M.S. 2] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
    - The Prisoner of Zenda (1924) lyrics by Herbert L. Fields
      - Curtain raiser act II/Introduction to Opening act I begin see: Finale act I
      - Finale act I, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p.; Note: 4 measure sketch at bottom of page; On back: crossed out holograph piano score in pencil headed "Curtain raiser act II/Introduction to Opening act I begin:"; at the bottom of this page is the beginning of a melody for "Finale act II" (Box-folder 13/27)
      - Make way, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 13/28)
      - March, Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p.; On cover: holograph scoring and copying instructions (Box-folder 13/29)
      - My king can do no wrong: act one, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 6 p. (Box-folder 13/30)
      - My king can do no wrong: act II, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p.; On back: holograph scoring and copying instructions (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Oh, dear!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Oh! dear: opening act I, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Note: at the bottom of p. [1] and on p. [2] are a crossed out holograph sketch for "Yankee-doodle (Countermelody)" and its 3-part realization (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Opening act III, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [5] p. (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Russian melody, Holograph sketches in pencil, some crossed out; [2] p.; Uniform title: Song of Russia (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Trio act one, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 13/34)
      - When men are in love, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 4 p. (Box-folder 13/35)
      - Will never do, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 13/36)
      - Without your love, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; Uniform title: Without love (Box-folder 13/37)
      - The worst of friends, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 13/38)
      - Yankee-doodle (Counter melody) see: Oh, dear!
    - Rex (1976) lyrics by Sheldon Harnick
      - [As once I loved you], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 14/1)
      - As once I loved you, Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Away from you: intro, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Away from you, Holograph lead sheet/sketch in pencil, with lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Away from you, Holograph lead sheet/sketch in pencil, with lyric; 2 p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Away from you: reprise, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Away from you: partial reprise, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/2)
      - The chase, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in pencil; [3] p.; Typed lyric sheet; 3 p. (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Christmas at Hampton Court, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Note: p. 6 consists of melody and lyric only; Typed lyric sheet; 3 p. (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Come to court, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Dear Jane, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Typed lyric sheet; 3 p. (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Don't come to court, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 3 p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Lizzie's lullaby, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Elizabeth (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Lizzie's lullaby, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Elizabeth, Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Eternal stars, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p.; Note: additional holograph sketch material on [2] p. at end; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/9)
      - At the field of cloth of gold, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p.; Note: piano accompaniment is incomplete; Typed lyric sheet; 4 p.; Includes: "Introduction" "Where is my son?" "[The field of cloth of gold]"; Uniform title: The field of cloth of gold (Box-folder 14/10)
      - From afar see: [Lyric sheets for Rex]
      - Henry Catherine scene: as in "Where is my son", Holograph lead sheet/piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/11)
      - I brought you a gift, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 3 p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/12)
      - I'll miss you See also: "Te Deum", Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/13)
      - In time, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; At end: sketch idea for 1st ending; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/14)
      - In time: reprise, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Kings, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Kings: reprise, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/15)
      - My daughter: [My daughter -- I], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Note: p. 2 is incomplete; Typed lyric sheet; 3 p. (Box-folder 14/16)
      - My daughter: [My daughter -- II], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Note: bottom half of p. 4 is ms. sketch material with some lyric; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/16)
      - No song more pleasing, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/17)
      - No song more pleasing: reprise, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/17)
      - The pears of Anjou, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 8 p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Rex, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 2 p.; Note: 2 measure holograph sketch in pencil on p. [3]; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Henry Anne duet, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p. (incomplete); Note: cut before New York opening; same music as "From afar"; At end: holograph sketch for 1st ending in pencil; Uniform title: So much you loved me (Box-folder 14/20)
      - So much you loved me, Typed lyric sheets (2 versions); [1] p. each (Box-folder 14/20)
      - Te Deum, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 3 p.; On back: holograph melodic sketch in pencil for "I'll miss you"; Typed lyric sheets (2 versions): [1] p. each (Box-folder 14/21)